50% hero. 100% cotton.
Captain Underpants: The First Epic Movie is a family,
comedy, animation film directed by David Soren.
Based on the bestselling book series, this outrageous comedy tells the story of George and Harold,  two overly imaginative pranksters
who hypnotize their principal into thinking he’s an enthusiastic, yet dimwitted, superhero named Captain Underpants.
George Beard (voice), played by Kevin Hart.
Harold Hutchins (voice), played by Thomas Middleditch.
Mr. Krupp / Captain Underpants (voice), played by Ed Helms.
Professor Poopypants (voice), played by Nick Kroll.
Melvin (voice), played by Jordan Peele.
Edith (voice), played by Kristen Schaal.
Captain Underpants: The First Epic Movie is a 2017 American animated
superhero comedy film produced by DreamWorks Animation.
Based on the children's novel series Captain Underpants, the film was directed by David Soren and written by
Nicholas Stoller, and stars the voices of Kevin Hart, Ed Helms, Thomas Middleditch, and Nick Kroll.
In the film, two fourth-grade pranksters named George and Harold
hypnotize their mean, humorless principal named Mr.
Krupp into thinking he is a superhero named Captain Underpants.
Captain Underpants: The First Epic Movie premiered at the Regency Village Theater in Los Angeles on May 21,
2017, and was released theatrically in the United States on June 2, by 20th Century Fox.
The film received positive reviews from critics and grossed
$125 million against a budget of $38 million.
A spin-off television series, The Epic Tales of Captain Underpants, was
released in 2018, and a spin-off film, Dog Man, was released in 2025.
The film explores themes of friendship, based on novel
or book, superhero, underwear, villain.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking and intense.